<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim Huang</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tim Huang</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:30:48 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building a new website (again)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-website-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:30:48 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-website-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;hello-world&#34;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s Tim, again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve built many personal websites. I&amp;rsquo;ve tried so many different tools - from pure HTML/CSS static sites deployed on Github Pages, to heavy duty CMS&amp;rsquo;s like Wordpress, to Jekyll, back to Wordpress, and now &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m using Hugo.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that for my needs (writing quick blog posts, on the fly), I want to prioritize my website&amp;rsquo;s speed and simplicity. I also want to save some money. So no more hosting service for now. We&amp;rsquo;re going back to good old static sites, backed up with a nice framework that will help me keep my content organized. And most importantly, fast.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 things I love to spend money on</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/5-things-i-love-to-spend-money-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/5-things-i-love-to-spend-money-on/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most popular posts of all time on r/financialindependence is to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/financialindependence/comments/58j8pc/build_the_life_you_want_then_save_for_it/?utm_source=timhuang.beehiiv.com&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=5-things-i-love-to-spend-money-on&#34;&gt;Build the life you want, then save for it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The general message is that instead of cutting back on everything (lattes, trips, etc.) to save for an ambiguous idea of what your life might look like in 20 years, you should invest in building a life that makes you feel more fulfilled today. That way, you have something you actually want to save for.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Coast FIRE is my favorite financial milestone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-coast-fire-is-my-favorite-milestone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-coast-fire-is-my-favorite-milestone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coast FIRE is one of my favorite ideas in personal finance, and it’s a milestone that I think will resonate with my fellow Gen Z.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For those not familiar with the term, FIRE = Financial Independence, Retire Early. The FIRE movement initially gained traction in the early 2010s, particularly among people working high income jobs in tech who lived frugal lifestyles. This combination allowed FIRE practitioners to aggressively invest for retirement, with the target of saving over 25x of their annual expenses to be considered “financially independent”. If they hit this milestone early enough, they could “retire early”, often in their 30s or 40s.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Journal #2 - Discovering North Carolina and Attending a Meat Conference</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-journal-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-journal-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last week, I got the chance to travel all throughout North Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I spent 3 days in Raleigh, 3 days in Boone (for the MEAT 🍖 conference), 0.5 day in Greensboro, and 3 days in Charlotte.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Charlotte → Raleigh → Boone → Greensboro → Charlotte&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-discovering-north-carolina&#34;&gt;⛰️ Discovering North Carolina&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-north-carolina-is-green&#34;&gt;1. North Carolina is green!!!&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Apparently North Carolina’s climate is considered sub-tropical, and even in the cities it was dense with trees and insects (so many beetles). To me, the weather felt similar to Hawaii - it was warm and humid, with occasional random showers in the middle of the day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Journal #1 - The one where I stayed in airports all day</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-journal-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel-journal-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had quite a wild travel itinerary this week.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I went from Vancouver to San Francisco, San Francisco to Calgary, Calgary to Vancouver, Vancouver to Charlotte, and then Charlotte to Raleigh, hitting a total of 5 different airports in less than 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;7/23: YVR → SFO&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;7/25: SFO → YYC&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;7/25: YYC → YVR&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;7/26 - 7/27: YVR → CLT&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;7/27: CLT → RDU&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I originally flew in to Vancouver on 7/20, but due to a family emergency, my trip to Vancouver was cut short and I ended up flying back to Pleasanton for a few days (7/23-7/25).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I overcame my limiting beliefs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-i-overcame-limiting-beliefs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-i-overcame-limiting-beliefs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello friends, welcome to my first newsletter post!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After procrastinating for years, I’ve decided it’s finally time for me to start a newsletter. Credit to my friend Manan who started his own newsletter recently for inspiring me to get started.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-am-i-doing-this&#34;&gt;Why am I doing this?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have a couple of goals for this newsletter (in no particular order):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start creating instead of consuming and help people at scale.&lt;/strong&gt; For a long time, I’ve been in “learn” mode about topics that interest me. Even though there’s still a ton for me to learn, I’ve hit a point where people have started to ask me questions and ask for help (which I’m more than happy to provide). I’d love to make the information I share during 1:1 conversations more widely available to others, and I figure the easiest way to do so is by writing and posting it to the internet 🙂&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
